{
  "tweet_id": "ce7b4b630ec44a7b839",
  "original_text": "On #ThisDayInHistory in 2016, actress Carrie Fisher, best known for portraying Princess Leia in 𝑆𝑡𝑎𝑟 𝑊𝑎𝑟𝑠, dies at 60 years old. Her death came after she had a heart attack four days earlier on a flight from London. Fisher, the daughter of Hollywood stars Debbie Reynolds and Eddie Fisher, began her career in 1975 with 𝑆ℎ𝑎𝑚𝑝𝑜𝑜 and rose to fame as Leia in the 1977 𝑆𝑡𝑎𝑟 𝑊𝑎𝑟𝑠. Her portrayal of the strong, independent princess became iconic.Fisher's other notable roles included parts in  𝑇ℎ𝑒 𝐵𝑙𝑢𝑒𝑠 𝐵𝑟𝑜𝑡ℎ𝑒𝑟𝑠 and 𝑊ℎ𝑒𝑛 𝐻𝑎𝑟��𝑦 𝑀𝑒𝑡 𝑆𝑎𝑙𝑙𝑦. She also worked as a script doctor for films like 𝑇ℎ𝑒 𝑊𝑒𝑑𝑑𝑖𝑛𝑔 𝑆𝑖𝑛𝑔𝑒𝑟 and 𝑆𝑖𝑠𝑡𝑒𝑟 𝐴𝑐𝑡. In 2015, Fisher returned to her 𝑆𝑡𝑎𝑟 𝑊𝑎𝑟𝑠 role in 𝑇ℎ𝑒 𝐹𝑜𝑟𝑐𝑒 𝐴𝑤𝑎𝑘𝑒𝑛𝑠.",
  "named_entities": [
    {
      "text": "2016",
      "type": "DATE"
    },
    {
      "text": "Carrie Fisher",
      "type": "PERSON"
    },
    {
      "text": "𝑆𝑡𝑎𝑟 𝑊𝑎𝑟𝑠",
      "type": "PERSON"
    },
    {
      "text": "60 years old",
      "type": "DATE"
    },
    {
      "text": "four days earlier",
      "type": "DATE"
    },
    {
      "text": "London",
      "type": "GPE"
    },
    {
      "text": "Hollywood",
      "type": "GPE"
    },
    {
      "text": "Debbie Reynolds",
      "type": "FAC"
    },
    {
      "text": "Eddie Fisher",
      "type": "PERSON"
    },
    {
      "text": "1975",
      "type": "DATE"
    },
    {
      "text": "𝑆ℎ𝑎𝑚𝑝𝑜𝑜",
      "type": "GPE"
    },
    {
      "text": "1977",
      "type": "DATE"
    },
    {
      "text": "𝑆𝑡𝑎𝑟 𝑊𝑎𝑟𝑠.",
      "type": "EVENT"
    },
    {
      "text": "Fisher",
      "type": "ORG"
    },
    {
      "text": "𝑇ℎ𝑒 𝐵𝑙𝑢𝑒𝑠 𝐵𝑟𝑜𝑡ℎ𝑒𝑟𝑠",
      "type": "PERSON"
    },
    {
      "text": "𝑊ℎ𝑒𝑛 𝐻𝑎𝑟",
      "type": "PERSON"
    },
    {
      "text": "𝑇ℎ𝑒 𝑊𝑒𝑑𝑑𝑖𝑛𝑔",
      "type": "PERSON"
    },
    {
      "text": "𝑆𝑖𝑛𝑔𝑒𝑟",
      "type": "PERSON"
    },
    {
      "text": "𝑆𝑖𝑠𝑡𝑒𝑟",
      "type": "PERSON"
    },
    {
      "text": "2015",
      "type": "DATE"
    },
    {
      "text": "Fisher",
      "type": "PERSON"
    },
    {
      "text": "𝑆𝑡𝑎𝑟 𝑊𝑎𝑟𝑠",
      "type": "PERSON"
    },
    {
      "text": "𝑇ℎ𝑒 𝐹𝑜𝑟𝑐𝑒",
      "type": "PERSON"
    }
  ],
  "capital_words": [
    "Carrie",
    "Fisher",
    "Princess",
    "Leia",
    "Her",
    "London",
    "Fisher",
    "Hollywood",
    "Debbie",
    "Reynolds",
    "Eddie",
    "Fisher",
    "Leia",
    "Her",
    "Fisher",
    "She",
    "In",
    "Fisher"
  ],
  "symbols": [
    "#ThisDayInHistory"
  ],
  "important_nouns": [
    "ThisDayInHistory",
    "actress",
    "years",
    "death",
    "heart",
    "attack",
    "days",
    "flight",
    "daughter",
    "career",
    "fame",
    "portrayal",
    "princess",
    "roles",
    "parts",
    "script",
    "doctor",
    "films",
    "role"
  ],
  "significant_verbs": [
    "known",
    "portraying",
    "dies",
    "came",
    "stars",
    "began",
    "rose",
    "became",
    "included",
    "worked",
    "returned"
  ],
  "unique_identifiers": [
    "Hollywood",
    "Leia",
    "Fisher",
    "𝑊ℎ𝑒𝑛 𝐻𝑎𝑟",
    "ThisDayInHistory",
    "𝑆𝑡𝑎𝑟 𝑊𝑎𝑟𝑠",
    "London",
    "𝑆𝑖𝑛𝑔𝑒𝑟",
    "𝑇ℎ𝑒 𝑊𝑒𝑑𝑑𝑖𝑛𝑔",
    "Carrie Fisher"
  ],
  "tweet_identity": "Hollywood script Leia attack Fisher",
  "detected_themes": {
    "conflit": [
      "attack"
    ],
    "celebrite": [
      "rip",
      "RIP",
      "death"
    ]
  },
  "username": "mikecollins"
}